Seidenberg, Jacob Additional Arbitration Files 5031 A&B
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
1949-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Seidenberg, Jacob
5031 A&B
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Case files and awards of Jacob Seidenberg pertaining to the Railroad Board of Adjustment.
3113402
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 22, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 28, 2016
Biographical / Historical
Dr. Jacob Seidenberg (1914-1996) was a government official who specialized in labor arbitration and non-discrimination contracts, and wrote extensively on labor law and negotiations. He graduated from Temple University in 1937 and received a law degree from the University of Pennsylvania Law School in 1941. During the 1940s he was an attorney with the U.S. War Department, the National War Labor Board and the National Wage Stabilization Board. In 1948 he went to graduate school at Cornell University, from which he earned his Ph.D. in industrial and labor relations in 1951. In 1951 he joined the staff of the President's Committee on Government Contract Compliance. The Committee was abolished by President Dwight D. Eisenhower in August 1953 by Executive Order 10479 and was succeeded by the President's Committee on Government Contracts. Seidenberg was appointed Executive Director of the new committee and served until January 1960 when he resigned to become a full-time labor arbitrator. The Committee was responsible for enforcing non-discrimination clauses in government contracts, worked with private businesses to help them overcome job discrimination, and developed educational programs against ethnic and racial discrimination. The chairman was Vice President Richard Nixon, and the vice chairman was Secretary of Labor James P. Mitchell. In later years Seidenberg served on a number of boards of inquiry involving labor disputes. From 1970 to 1975 he was chairman of the Federal Services Impasses Panel which settled deadlocks in federal labor negotiations.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5032: Jacob Seidenberg Injunction Study 5175: Jacob Seidenberg Taft-Hartley Maritime Dispute Records 5194: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Files 5217: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Case Files 5229: Jacob Seidenberg Additional records 5468: Jacob Seidenberg Arbitration files 5519: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5571: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5605: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5635: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5666: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5706: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5756: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5773: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5808: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5900: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5935: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files 5953: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Records 5988: Jacob Seidenberg Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial.; Seidenberg, Jacob.
3113402
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Case and Awards. Disputes involving the St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company. (Box 1-3(A))
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.100 Award No. 249-286, 1964-1966 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Brotherhood of Railway Trainmen and St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.100 Award No.250, 1960-1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 2)
    Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Case No. 765-60. BRT and St. Louis Southwestern Railway Company.
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 249, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 3)
    Includes: Maps Of Mississippi. BRT and St Louis Southwestern Railway Company(STLSW)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.100 Award No. 251, 1959-1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 4)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 252, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 5)
    Includes: photo documents and advertisement of cars magazine
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 253, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 6)
    Includes telegraphic report of accident
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 254, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 7)
    BRT Case 946-62
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No.255, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 8)
    BRT Case No. 419- 57
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 256, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 9)
    Includes: a sketched map
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 267-258, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 10)
    BRT Case No. 408-57 and 410-57
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 259, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 11)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 260, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 12)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 261, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 13)
    Includes a business card of train rates and fees
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 262, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 14)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No.263, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 15)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 265, 1963-1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 16)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 266, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 17)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 267, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 18)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 267-268, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 19)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 269, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 20)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 270, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 21)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 270-271, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 22)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 272-274, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 23)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 275-277, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 24)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 278, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 25)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 281, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 26)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 282, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 27)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 283, 1968 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 28)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 284, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 29)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 285, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 30)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 100 Award No. 286, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 31)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.1, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 32)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-106
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.2, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 33)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-107
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.3, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 34)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-108
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.4, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 35)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-109
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.5, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 36)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-189
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.6, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 37)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No.T-63-190 and applies to 192- 197
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.7, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 38)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-64-40
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.8, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 39)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-384 and T-63-406
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.9, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 40)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-355 and T-64-401
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.10, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 41)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-390 and T-64-406
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.11, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 42)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-371 to T-64-404.
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.12, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 43)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-3 to T-64-409
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.13, 1964 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 44)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-64-20 to T-64-429
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No.14, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 45)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-64-297 and T-64-300
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.560 Award No. 15, 1965 (Box 1-3(A), Folder 46)
    Carrier's Submission Claim No. T-63-300
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.28-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 1)
  Pennsylvania Railroad Lines West. Docket No. TD-296
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.28-E, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 2)
  Pennsylvania Lines East. Docket No. 2043
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.29-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 3)
  Lines West. Docket No. TD-301
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.29-E, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 4)
  Lines East. Docket No. 2054
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.30-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 5)
  Pennsylvania Lines West. Docket No.TD-302
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.30-E, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 6)
  Pennsylvania Lines East. Docket No.2055
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.31-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 7)
  Penn Lines West. Docket No. TD-305
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.31-E, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 8)
  Pennsylvania Lines East. Docket No. 2056
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.32-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 9)
  Lines West. Docket No.TD-313
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.32-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 10)
  Lines East. Docket No. 2088. Pennsylvania Railroad Company diagram of tracks
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.32-E, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 11)
  Docket No. 2065
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.33-W, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 12)
  Docket No. TD-314
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.33-E, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 13)
  Docket No. 2075
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.34-W, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 14)
  Docket No.TD-325
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.34-E, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 15)
  Docket TD-2077
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.35-W, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 16)
  Docket No. TD-327
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.35-E, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 17)
  Docket No.2084
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.36-W, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 18)
  Docket No.TD-334
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.36-E, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 19)
  Docket No. 2087
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.37-W, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 20)
  Docket No. TD-374
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.38-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 21)
  Lines West. Docket No. TD-375
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.38-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 22)
  Docket No. 2094
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.39-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 23)
  Docket No. TD-382
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.39-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 24)
  Lines East. Docket No. 2098
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.40-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 25)
  Lines East. Docket No.TD-204
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.40-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 26)
  Lines West. Docket No. TD-388
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.41-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 27)
  Lines West. Docket No. TD-390. Includes: A train map
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.41-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 28)
  Docket No. TD-218
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.42-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 29)
  Docket No. TD-391. Includes: Photo documents
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.42-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 30)
  Docket No. TD-219
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.43-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 31)
  Docket No. TD-397
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.43-E, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 32)
  Docket No. TD-273
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.44-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 33)
  Docket No. TD-322
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.45-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 34)
  Docket No. TD-339
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.44 and 45-W, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 35)
  Docket No. TD-398 and TD-399
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.46-W, 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 36)
  Docket No. TD-416
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.46-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 37)
  Docket No TD-341
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.47-E, 1966 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 38)
  Docket No. TD-349
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.47-W, 1965 (Box 4-6(A), Folder 39)
  Docket No. TD-317
- Liner Work Award no.1 Docket no.1642, 1959 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 1)
- Award no.1- L.E. (Docket 1752), 1966 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 2)
- Lines West- Award no.2, 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 3)
- Award no.2 L.E. (Docket no.1776), 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 4)
- Lines West- Award no.3 Claim 1769, 1957 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 5)
- Award no.3 L.E. Docket no.1777, 1958 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 6)
- Award no.4 Claim 1792, Lines West, 1959 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 7)
- Award no.4 L.E. Docket 1828, 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 8)
- Award no.5 L.E. Docket 1885, 1959 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 9)
- Award no.5 Claim 1804-W, 1959 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 10)
- Award no.6 L.E. Docket no.1877, 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 11)
- Award no.7 Docket 1822-W, 1959 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 12)
- Award no.7 L.E. (Docket no.1890), 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 13)
- Award no.8 L.E. (Docket no.1897), 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 14)
- Award no.8 Claim 1837-W, 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 15)
- Award no.9 Docket no.1838-W, 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 16)
- Award no.9 L.E. (Docket no.1901), 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 17)
- Award no.10 Docket 1904, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 18)
- Award no.10 Docket no.1881-W, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 19)
- Award no.11-W Docket no.1895, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 20)
- Award no.11 L.E. Docket no.1914, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 21)
- Award no.17 L.E. Docket no.1934, 1958 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 22)
- Award no.12-W Claim no.1923, 1958 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 23)
- Award no.13-W Docket 1928, 1965 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 24)
- Award no.13 L.E. Docket no.1943, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 25)
- Award no.14 L.E. Docket no.1944, 1958 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 26)
- Award no.14-W Docket 1930, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 27)
- Award no.15-W Docket 1933, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 28)
- Award no.15 Docket 1945, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 29)
- Award no.16- L.E. Docket no.1960, 1956-1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 30)
- Award 16-W Docket no.1973, 1944-1965 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 31)
- Award no.17-W Docket 1987, 1959 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 32)
- Award no.17- L.E. System Docket no.1963, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 33)
- Award no.18-W Docket no.1998, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 34)
- Award no.18- June Ent, System Docket no.1965, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 35)
- Award no.19-W Docket no.1999, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 36)
- Award no.19- L.E. System Docket no.1967, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 37)
- Award no.20-W Docket 2012, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 38)
- Award no.20- Line East System Docket 1968, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 39)
- Award no.21- L.E. System Docket no.2017, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 40)
- Award 21-W Docket 2025 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 41)
- Award no.22-W Docket 2044, 1962 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 42)
- Award no.22-L.E. System Docket no.2021, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 43)
- Award 23-W Docket no.2062, 1962 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 44)
- Award no.24-W Docket no.2063, 1962 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 45)
- Award no.24-L.E. System Docket no.2028 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 46)
- Award no.25-W Docket 2073, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 47)
- Award no.25- L.E. System Docket no.2031, 1962 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 48)
- Award no.26-W Docket 2091, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 49)
- Award no.26-L.E. System Docket no.2036, 1962 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 50)
- Award no.27- L.E. System Docket no.2038, 1960 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 51)
- Award no.27-W, 1961 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 52)
- Award no.6 Docket 1818-W, 1959 (Box 1-3(B), Folder 53)
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 589. Arbitrations and Awards between Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Pennsylvania Railroad Company Lines East or Lines West. Years: 1965-1966 (Box 4-6(B))
- Special Board of Adjustment No. 589. Arbitration and Awards between Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Pennsylvania Railroad Company Lines East or West. Years: 1966-1967 (Box 7-9(B))
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.48-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 1)
    Docket No. TD-341
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.48-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 2)
    Docket No. TD-430
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.49-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 3)
    Docket No. TD-387
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.49-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 4)
    Docket No. TD-530
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.50-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 5)
    Docket No. TD-555
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 50-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 6)
    Docket No. TD-412
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.51-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 7)
    Docket No. TD-561
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.51-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 8)
    Docket No. TD-414
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.52-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 9)
    Docket No. TD-636
  - Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.53-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 10)
    Docket No. TD-443
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No.53-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 11)
    Docket No. TD-659
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 54-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 12)
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 54-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 13)
    Docket No. TD-665
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 55-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 14)
    Docket No.TD-666
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 55-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 15)
    Docket No. TD-464. Includes: pamphlets, and photo documents
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 56-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 16)
    Docket No. 2452
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 56-E, 1965-1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 17)
    Docket No. TD-465
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 57-E, 1965 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 18)
    Docket No.TD-507
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 57-W, 1967-1968 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 19)
    Docket No. 2389
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 58-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 20)
    Docket No. 2453
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 68-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 21)
    Docket No. TM-101. Includes: Other related documents
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 59-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 22)
    Docket No. 2329
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 59-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 23)
    Docket No. 2095
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 60-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 24)
    Docket No. 2451
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 60-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 25)
    Docket No. 2099
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 61-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 26)
    Docket No. TD-447
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 61-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 27)
    Docket No. 2100
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 61-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 28)
    Docket No. TD-456
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 62-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 29)
    Docket No. 2101
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 63-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 30)
    Docket No. TD 493
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 63, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 31)
    Docket No. 2104
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 64-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 32)
    Docket No. TD-494
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 64-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 33)
    Docket No. 2108
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No. 65-W, 1967 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 34)
    Docket No. TD-498
  - Special Board of Adjustment No. 589 Award No.65-E, 1966 (Box 7-9(B), Folder 35)
    Docket No. 2115
- Award no.66- L- W, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 1)
- Award no.66 Docket no.2117, 1962 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 2)
- Award no.67- L- W System Docket TD-524, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 3)
- Award no.67 Docket 2108, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 4)
- Award no.68- L- W System Docket TD-536, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 5)
- Award no.68+ 69 Docket 2120-2121, 1962 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 6)
- Award no.69- L- W System Docket TD-538, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 7)
- Award no.70- L- W System Docket TD-550, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 8)
- Award no.71- L- W TD-453, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 9)
- Award no.71- L- E Docket 2128, 1962 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 10)
- Award no.72 System Docket TD-556, 1967 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 11)
- Award no.72- L- E Docket no.2149, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 12)
- Award no.73 System Docket TD-559, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 13)
- Award no.73- L- E Docket no.2150, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 14)
- Award no.74 System Docket TD-564, 1962 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 15)
- Award no.74- L- E Docket no.2152, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 16)
- Award no.75 System Docket 572, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 17)
- Award no.75 L- E Docket no.2153, 1959 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 18)
- Award no.76- L- W TD-581, 1967 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 19)
- Award no.76- L- E Docket no.2154, 1959 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 20)
- Award no.77- L- W TD-581, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 21)
- Award no.72- L- E Docket no.2158, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 22)
- Award no.78- L- W TD-602, 1965 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 23)
- Award no.78- L- E Docket no.2165, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 24)
- Award no.79 L- W TD-620, 1965 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 25)
- Award no.79- L- E Docket no.2167, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 26)
- Award no.80- L- W TD-621, 1965 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 27)
- Award no.80 L-E System Docket no.2170, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 28)
- Award no.81- L- W, 1949 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 29)
- Award no.81 L- E Docket no.2180, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 30)
- Awards 82- 83- L- W, 1965 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 31)
- Award no.82- L- E Docket no.2184, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 32)
- Award no.83 L- E Docket no.2185, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 33)
- Award no.84- L- E Docket no.2203, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 34)
- Award no.84 L- W TD 1723, 1960 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 35)
- Award no. L- W TD-1725, 1957 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 36)
- Annual no.85- L- E Docket no.2204, 1961 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 37)
- Annual no.86 L- W TD 1873, 1960 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 38)
- Award no.86- L- E Docket no.2207, 1963 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 39)
- Award 87- L- W TD-2049, 1969 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 40)
- Award no.87- L- E Docket 2208, 1963-1967 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 41)
- Award no.88 L- W TD 2053, 1962 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 42)
- Award no.88- L- E, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 43)
- Award no.89- L- W TD-2130, 1962 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 44)
- Award no.89- L- E, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 45)
- Award no.90 L- W TD 2143, 1961-1962 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 46)
- Award no.90 Docket no.2322, 1964 (Box 10-12(B), Folder 47)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.91-W, 1967 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 1)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.91-E, 1966 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 2)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.92-W, 1967 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 3)
- Special Board of Adjustment No.589 Award No.92-E, 1966 (Box 13-15(B), Folder 4)